allsides.com 2017-06-15

# Privacy Policy | AllSides

#### AllSides, Inc. Privacy Policy

We at AllSides believe in protecting the privacy of your personally identifiable information. Therefore, we have put together this Privacy Policy to inform you of how we plan to use your information and protect it. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on allsides.com. We will post updates to the Privacy Policy here with so please check back from time to time to view any updates.

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey or fill out a form. The information we collect is used to create an account – email, userid and password. We also collect personal information such as First Name and Last Name and a photo which are all optional. You may also visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for?

The information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our Website(we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors in aggregate. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. No personally identifiable information will be shared.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'Edit Account' page.

#### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Website and not to information collected offline.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Website.

#### Your Consent

By using our Website, you consent to our Website Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on August 24, 2012

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

AllSides, Inc.  
PO Box 590751  
San Francisco, California 94159 USA  
info@allsides.com
